Every time the rain no longer falls,
and I see the sky,
I think back to when I was
a child Who could only cry,
blindly chasing after
him I fell far behind
my only thought One day I will be stronger
Bridery and gratitude fading with the
wind Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure, but until I do.
My voyage will not end.
No matter what's next!
I'm walking straight ahead.
So let's go!
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's all on our side,
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, But we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything.
We'll take what I hold dear away from me?
The voices inside me.
Push me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through.
No matter what I gotta do!
The fiercest of all can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the world?
Would I turn back?
Oh, let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now!
Though time's not on our side,
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall, But we'll
always keep on standing.
There's no way anything Will take
what I hold dear away from me!
I know the future's there for us to see.
Make your way to the scaffold!
Watch your backs!
The giant unit's moving out!
They're trying to head off Oars Jr!
Time to live up to our duty!
He can't defeat us all!
That thing is impossibly huge!
He's at least twice as
big as a common giant!
Keep shooting!
He's a living creature!
Bullets should stop him!
I can't say we were expecting
such a powerful beast.
Shoot him!
Fill up with land!
Ors, don't do this!
You're an easy target for them!
Please turn around!
Hang on, Ace.
I'm coming for you!
Ah, holy crap!
Kill that beast!
Boys, open up a path for
us to get into the bay!
Take the bay and then the plaza!
Damn it all! Fall back!
Tighten up the defensive line and
don't let them get to the plaza!
Stand down or die, Navy!
I swear.
What the hell are you doing?
We're at war here.
We don't have any use for the weak.
I've never had to crane my
head up to look at anyone!
Me neither.
That oars is just as
stubborn as he ever was.
Getting yourself killed
does not make you brave!
Don't stop me, Pops!
I won't stop!
Cause I don't wanna!
Not until I'm done!
Not until Serious!
I wanna save my bro!
I want to do it now so
it doesn't hurt go there.
I know the feeling.
All right, men.
Help out the big guy.
Go cover oars. Yeah!
Howie was supposed to fight that thing?
He's too big.
Don't worry, Vice Admiral.
I'll avenge you. Ah!
Horse is one hell of a destruction.
Let's make our move!
Slave Arrow!
Oh! Wait, what?
They're statues!
So, you're the pirate empress, huh?
What did you do to me?
I'm crumbling!
Curfew! Deer!
You psycho!
Why are you attacking the Marines?
I may have agreed to aid you in your
fight against Whitebeard's crew,
but I don't recall making any
promises about collateral damage.
Allies or foes, all men
are equally worthless.
Well, except for one.
You can hate me if you want, but you
can't say that I didn't keep my word.
You're nuts!
Won't you at least take
mercy on my beauty?
Why not?
Ah, damn it!
I'm gonna save you now, Ace!
Stop!
One, one, one, one, one.
Prepare yourself for the Ursa Shock.
Stop!
Oars, that's enough!
You made this.
Yeah, some folks I met in the
Wano Kingdom taught me how.
Try it on.
Ace ruined two others before
he got that one right.
They burned to a crisp.
That's what happens when someone
who's made a fire weaves straw.
Oh, a slice of coal under here.
Then it works.
I like the look.
AIM AND FIRE!
OARS!
Run away, man!
You're an easy target now!
Hey, Captain Oars, what are
you doing outside in the rain?
Rain or shine, I'm doing fine.
I don't get wet anymore.
Wow, I love this hat.
If I can't save you,
at least I can take out
one of the warlords!
Why'd you stop?
Ace is right there.
Ow, my foot.
Captain!
Captain! Hey, Captain!
You're going to stay outside again?
Why should I care?
The snow's not getting on my head.
In the heat or the cold.
This head never gets old.
You're the best, eh?
Now that was fun.
Horse!
Wait, he's still moving?
I thought he was...
He's infiltrated the plaza!
Gotta go a little bit more!
Don't worry, Ace!
I can make it for sure!
That damn Doe Flamingo!
He knew I wanted ores intact!
You don't cut the foot off
a corpse that once claimed!
Doppelman!
Finish him!
Spocky Shadow Lizard!
No!
See, now that's how you do it.
That is some good murder.
No, Captain Ors!
Damn you, you warlord scumbag! Captain!
Ors, no!
Arse!
I'll have to fix up that foot of his,
but that's a small price to
pay for another giant zombie.
This is the foot.
Oh, oars.
Shouldn't drop your guard, Whitebeard!
Bicep Hulans!
Help me...
Okay...
Everybody just leave
Whitebeard alone, I guess.
Now climb up war's body and charge!
This is beautiful.
To Flamingo,
you're going to pay for what you did to
Boris, and I'm going to collect the debt.
What the hell are you laughing at?
How are you not laughing?
We're standing on the
fulcrum of history itself.
The future and past will be written here.
Put your hammer in the dark!
Take him down, boss!
Stop dancing around and fight for real!
I can't do this.
I'm scared and I'm weak and I'm useless.
Even our leaders are
falling one after another.
There's no way a loser like me
is going to survive out there.
Wait, Kuma.
I'm running away too.
Get back to the battlefield.
Just let me go!
Please, sir!
What's Admiral Akainu doing here?
I can't die like this!
I'm terrified to leave
my family on their own!
Please!
I'm begging you, Admiral!
As soldiers of the Navy,
we carry the weight of the
justice of the world on our backs,
and will gladly die to defend it.
Any man who turns tail and runs doesn't
deserve to call himself a marine,
let alone a man for that matter.
The most he could be
called is a waste of life.
If you truly care about your family as
you say, you'll only shame them by living.
No!
He killed one of his own soldiers?
Admiral Sakazuki, we're ready
to proceed with the operation.
Excellent.
It's finally time.
The operation?
Haze!
I don't understand, Commander. Why?
He's got control of my body!
Delphamiga, you bastard!
Stop it! Please, no!
Pirates are evil.
The Navy is just.
But that's only true
because history tells us so.
Children who've never
known peace have different
values than children
who've never known war.
The one who wins will rewrite the
definition of right and wrong.
They'll decide the future
and how the past is written.
Will justice prevail?
Why, there's no other way!
The winner will define
the meaning of justice.
Go!
Everyone get to the space oars bay!
The bay is out!
A knife cutter?
It's the ice witch, Wado Bay!
I've cut plenty of
glaciers tougher than that.
All right, let's move!
The path is open! Right
behind you! All clear!
It's time to move into the bay!
They've broken through the bay
head at two different points, sir!
There's nothing left to prevent Whitebeard's
allies from entirely flooding the area!
I'm afraid we've got no
way to hold them back, sir!
What should we do now?
Don't worry about it.
We're ready.
Put the plan into action.
It's about time.
Out of the way!
Either stand down or die!
Move it, you old bag!
I can't wash!
I can't put out the dry!
I feel so fresh and clean!
Sorry, boys, maybe try again
in a couple hundred years.
Put a call out to all ships and soldiers.
Of course, he's got a plan up his sleeve.
You've always been
resourceful, Buddha Sengoku.
Old man!
What are you doing up here?
Not having second thoughts, are you?
No, they chose to be pirates.
They brought this upon themselves.
In that case... Shut up!
I don't want to talk.
I just want to sit here.
Little idiot!
Morons!
I don't want either of
you becoming pirates!
Hey, don't hit Luffy!
Mean old fart! Oh, what?
Ace, you come here!
I have no sympathy in me for criminals.
But family is a different story.
Now what?
What am I supposed to do?
Ace, you fool Why couldn't you have just
listened to me and done what I asked?
Ace, trust me on this.
You two really should join the Navy.
Okay?
I know you'll make a strong Navy soldier.
If you're feeling any doubt
over what must be done,
I'm afraid I just can't
take pity on you, Garp.
If I had doubts, I would
have done something already.
Did you hear what I just heard, Helmepo?
What their strategy is?
Yeah.
They're going to bypass the schedule
and immediately execute Firefist Ace.
But if they do that...
Huh?
What the...
Hm?
What is that?
Something's falling from the sky!
It's gotta be another surprise
ambush from Whitebeard!
You just have to overdo it every time!
This is because of his death wing!
Oh, so it's all my fault?
Who cares whose fault it is?
We're gonna die!
It's all frozen down there!
Oh, yeah, I'm rubber. I'll be fine.
Hey, what about us, you selfish jerk?
Do something already.
This is not how I picture myself dying.
Somebody help me, please.
I still care about whose fault this
is, and it's all yours, Straw Hat.
Damn you, though.
I'm hearing.
Please!